<?xml version="1.0"?>
<POLICIES xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2002/01/P3Pv1">
    <!-- Generated by IBM P3P Policy Editor version Beta 1.12 built 2/27/04 1:19 PM -->

    <!-- Expiry information for this policy -->
    <EXPIRY max-age="86400"/>

<POLICY
    name="bbpolicy"
    discuri="http://www.bookingbuddy.com/privacy.php"
    opturi="http://www.omniture.com/privacy/optout.html"
    xml:lang="en">
    <!-- Description of the entity making this policy statement. -->
    <ENTITY>
    <DATA-GROUP>
<DATA ref="#business.name">Attn: BookingBuddy.com</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.online.email">privacy@bookingbuddy.com</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.online.uri">http://www.bookingbuddy.com</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.telecom.telephone.number">617-886-5555</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.postal.street">500 Rutherford Avenue
Second Floor</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.postal.city">Boston</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.postal.stateprov">MA</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.postal.postalcode">02129</DATA>
<DATA ref="#business.contact-info.postal.organization">Smarter Travel Media LLC</DATA>
    </DATA-GROUP>
    </ENTITY>

    <!-- Disclosure -->
    <ACCESS><contact-and-other/></ACCESS>


    <!-- Disputes -->
    <DISPUTES-GROUP>
        <DISPUTES resolution-type="service" service="mailto:privacy@bookingbuddy.com" short-description="Business Assets">
            <LONG-DESCRIPTION>As part of operations, BookingBuddy may sell, transfer or merge particular businesses and/or other assets to a third party. As part of such a transaction, personal information users have provided to BookingBuddy may be given to a third party. BookingBuddy attempts to comply with all legislative and judicial orders. These orders will take precedence over the details stated in the policy above. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or your dealings with BookingBuddy, please contact:

Smarter Travel Media LLC
Attn: BookingBuddy.com
500 Rutherford Avenue
Second Floor
Boston, MA 02129
617-886-5555
617-886-5501 (fax)
privacy@bookingbuddy.com</LONG-DESCRIPTION>
            <REMEDIES><correct/></REMEDIES>
        </DISPUTES>
    </DISPUTES-GROUP>

    <!-- Statement for group "Smarter Travel" -->
    <STATEMENT>
        <EXTENSION optional="yes">
            <GROUP-INFO xmlns="http://www.software.ibm.com/P3P/editor/extension-1.0.html" name="Smarter Travel"/>
        </EXTENSION>

    <!-- Consequence -->
    <CONSEQUENCE>
BookingBuddy's registration form may require users to provide basic contact and demographic information. We use or may use your contact information (such as email address) from the registration form to send you newsletters and occasional information about our services and partners, inform you if you are the potential winner of a contest or promotion, personalize your experience with BookingBuddy, or investigate cases of suspected fraud or abuse. You may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the Opting-Out of Further Communications section below.

In the future, in order to customize your experience with our email newsletters, we may receive a confirmation when you open email from BookingBuddy if your computer supports such capabilities. Clicking on a link in a BookingBuddy newsletter may also be tracked on a per user basis to allow us to present content, which closely matches your interests. Demographic and profile data (such as state, zip code, age, or gender) may be used to customize your experience at our site or in our email newsletters, showing you content and advertising that may best suit your needs. This information is shared with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregate basis only. Individial user click behavior is never shared with advertisers and partners.

If, in the future, you enter BookingBuddy via a reward or incentive program, BookingBuddy may share your email address with the program through which you entered BookingBuddy to ensure you are credited with your incentive.

You may also register for BookingBuddy and/or specific BookingBuddy newsletters at web sites operated by third parties. These third parties may share contact, demographic or profile data that you voluntarily provide during the registration process with BookingBuddy. You also may provide personal information to third parties when you register at a third party web site and specifically request that your information be forwarded to us so that we can send you information about our product and service offerings. BookingBuddy does or may in the future use this information in the same manner as information collected directly by BookingBuddy. This Privacy Policy does not bind sites that collect information on behalf of BookingBuddy, and BookingBuddy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

To better serve you, we may also store information you present to us via email or telephone communications with BookingBuddy's Customer Service Department. This information is or may be used in the same manner as information directly collected using BookingBuddy's registration form. We may also use information you provide us via email or telephone to pursue the matter for which you contacted us. BookingBuddy also may obtain information from you in our online forums. This information may not be disclosed except as consistent with Terms of Use.

In order to better communicate with registered users about their registration status, BookingBuddy may acquire information about users from third-party sources, including but not limited to a users mailing address. The information collected will only be shared, if at all, on an aggregate basis only with third parties.

Email Communications: To help us make emails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open email from BookingBuddy if your computer supports such capabilities.</CONSEQUENCE>

    <!-- Use (purpose) -->
    <PURPOSE><admin required="opt-out"/><contact required="opt-out"/><current/><develop required="opt-out"/><pseudo-analysis required="opt-out"/><pseudo-decision required="opt-out"/><individual-analysis required="opt-out"/><individual-decision required="opt-out"/></PURPOSE>

    <!-- Recipients -->
    <RECIPIENT><ours/><other-recipient/><delivery/></RECIPIENT>

    <!-- Retention -->
    <RETENTION><indefinitely/></RETENTION>

    <!-- Base dataschema elements. -->
    <DATA-GROUP>
    <DATA ref="#dynamic.clickstream"/>
    <DATA ref="#dynamic.http"/>
    <DATA ref="#dynamic.cookies"/>
    </DATA-GROUP>
</STATEMENT>

<CONTEXT>
	<URL>www.bookingbuddy.com</URL>
	<ACCESSTIME>20110710</ACCESSTIME>
	<CREATIONTIME>20100702</CREATIONTIME>
</CONTEXT>

<ACTION>
	<ACCEPTED>false</ACCEPTED>
	<DOMAINS>www.ticketmaster.com</DOMAINS>
	<USEROVERRIDE>false</USEROVERRIDE>
</ACTION>

<!-- End of policy -->
</POLICY>
</POLICIES>

